One of them is lying. So is the other.
How to Lose a Guy in 10 Days is a comedy, romance
film directed by Donald Petrie.
It's the battle of wills, as Andie needs to prove she can dump a guy in 10
days, whereas Ben needs to prove he can win a girl in 10 days.
Now, the clock is ticking—and the wildly entertaining comedy smash is off and running in
this irresistible tale of sex, lies and outrageous romantic fireworks!
Andie Anderson, played by Kate Hudson.
Benjamin Barry, played by Matthew McConaughey.
Michelle Rubin, played by Kathryn Hahn.
Jeannie Ashcroft, played by Annie Parisse.
Tony, played by Adam Goldberg.
Thayer, played by Thomas Lennon.
How to Lose a Guy in 10 Days is a 2003 romantic comedy film directed by Donald Petrie, from a script by
Kristen Buckley, Brian Regan, and Burr Steers, and starring Kate Hudson and Matthew McConaughey.
Loosely based on the picture book of the same name by Michele Alexander and Jeannie Long, the plot concerns a
women's magazine writer and an advertising executive who both begin a relationship with ulterior motives.
While the story and characters in the film are original, the dating
"don'ts" of the picture book are included in the film.
How to Lose a Guy in 10 Days was released theatrically by Paramount Pictures in the United States on February 7, 2003, and in Germany
on April 17, 2003, and was a box office success, grossing $177.5 million against a production budget of $50 million.
The film received mixed reviews from critics, who praised Hudson and McConaughey's
acting and chemistry, but criticized the script and predictable plot.
The film explores themes of bet, new york city,
journalist, therapist, advertising expert.
The tone is lighthearted and emotional.